Oh, thank you for your time. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It was the height of production, you know.
It was an idea that only high intensity could have come up with.
Yes.
I thought, "This is something I would never have thought of.
So there is.
Idol people don't have such long deadlines,
The most important thing is what happens after 10 years.
I wonder who will be left after 10 years.
Are there any members who have worked together with you that you think are great?
I guess I would have to say yes.
You know...
I don't see why this guy can't sell.
Now then, Mr. Sakuma, the video you made when Norokaya-san came before was very well received.
Oh, yes, the various things Noro-san did during his AKB days.
No, it was very interesting.
Tylan.
How many kilos did you lie about?
Five kilometers.
And then he just flew up and fell.
Oh, my God.
Variety's brain works.
It's like, "Why not?
Like, "Why the hell not?
I'm telling you, I lied about my weight.
I thought I was going to die in the bungee.
So we've invited a certain former idol to join us again.
Legendary Idol
This is great.
I think you'll really learn a lot.
Well, let's invite him.
This is the gentleman. Please come in.
Hi. - Hi.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
You're ready early.
And now, our special guest this time is a former member of AKB48.
Ms. Shizuka Otani.
Pleased to meet you.
Yoshimura?
Of course.
I'm sure you've been to the theater.
I'm sure you've been to one before.
Crying already?
What?
You sounded like you were about to cry.
What do you think, Mr. Otani?
There's the Riffraff.
Of course I'm aware of it.
What? Really?
I've seen it on Youtube.
It's just...
Really...
Fanskills...
You're teaching me so much.
I don't think I can handle it in this world anymore.
I don't know...
What do you think of Rachlaff?
Well, it's really...
When I first became an idol.
"I'm an idol, but I want to say something interesting.
I feel like I'm watching that period of trial and error.
It makes my heart ache!
Mr. Otani, too.
The image I have of you on TV
You were in charge of variety.
Do you remember those days?
Yes, I remember.
It was sweet and sour.
It's like my youth.
I want to remember the funny things.
I want to remember what it was like before.
I feel like I'm watching my youth right now.
Yes.
I had a talk with Hal Kochi the other day.
I came up with a list of the top three.
The top three most popular, the top seven gods, and so on.
Kochiharu was in it.
But I don't know...
I had already decided on the top three or top four.
I always thought I had to do something different.
Kochiharu...
Isn't that right, Otani?
That's right.
If you don't stand out, you'll never stand out.
Well...
No one will look at you.
If you want to stand out, what do you do?
That's right.
With that in mind, she asked me what my dream was for the future.
Voice actor...
Actress, model, celebrity...
I circled it.
I circled "Oline.
I thought there probably weren't any.
But Akimoto-sensei actually thought there was a weird guy.
So he told me to take a picture of him.
Wow...Wow.
So it's all connected.
Yes, it is.
So, now that you're here...
I'd like to do something like this for this project.
Learn from Takatani
Take a quiz to learn how to become an idol!
Yay!
From the hard life as an underclassman
Now he's very active in variety shows and so on.
We're going to take a quiz and learn a few lessons from her.
to teach us a variety of lessons
I'm going to learn a lot of lessons from him.
And they're not justified lessons, right?
Yes, that's right.
That was rude.
I just said something rude at a very fast pace.
Basically, it's an idea that only the most ardent of people would come up with.
Yes.
I'm sure you wouldn't have come up with this one.
You know...
That's right.
So what you learn there will be useful for the legitimacy group as well, right?
It's definitely useful.
I see. So you're saying it's not really a legitimate group.
Don't push me in my sleep.
Don't push it in your sleep.
That's what the numbers are for this project.
Please do.
Let's start with the first one.
Yes, the first one is...
Lessons learned from the concert.
This is the most important, isn't it?
A concert is a moment of contact.
It's the place where you can see the most sparkling place.
It's the place where you can see the most sparkling place, so it's very important.
Yes, sir.
So here's a quiz!
Mr. Otani...
Every time when a concert starts
Mr. Otani would do a certain thing
What is it?
Something a super idol wouldn't do.
I don't think so.
I've never heard of it.
Yes, Natsume.
Big slice
That's lovey-dovey right now.
I'm not trying to guess.
You might get it right if you try.
Yes, Fujisaki.
Flip tricks.
You didn't do the big slash, did you?
No, I didn't do the big slash.
When you were a member...
Come on, Hayashi.
I messed with the fans.
That's Ms. Norokayo, isn't it?
That's Ms. Norokayo.
It was Norokayo who stopped messing with me.
Takanashi.
I disguise myself and hide in the audience to look for fans
I wouldn't do that.
But...
I'm close
Isearch.
Yes, Saitama
I shook his hand roughly with a handshake
When the curtain opened when it began
First thing I do
Nagamatsu
As soon as the show starts, I count my penlights.
Oh, that's too close!
So close! Nice!
One more back.
One more back of it.
Yes, Sasaki!
I'm going to wave my penlight right after the show starts!
No, not that way.
Hurry up!
What kind of people are you looking for?
Yes, Yoshimura.
Looking for a fan?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let me look for it.
Can you, Yuuchan?
I'll ask you who likes my parents.
Oh, I won't ask then.
But we're getting close.
Yes, Natsue.
I'm going to make funny faces at those who are holding my penlight.
I'll make funny faces one by one
Oh, no.
Like this.
No, I can't do that. I can't do that.
You can't do that.
Rust one.
Rust.
Yes, can you do it?Yes, I can.
Let's count the number of fans.
Fill in Excel
Play a trick.
I'm also in sales.
Parents, please answer correctly.
The correct answer is find a fan who is a perfect choreographer.
Yes, sir.
What does this mean?
I'm sure there's a fan or two in the audience who likes to copy the choreography.
I'm sure there are one or two people in the audience who like to copy the choreography.
That's why I find them the most.
I'm in the habit of doing "gao yuei".
Gao Yue...
It's a habit.
It's a nasty-sounding habit.
I have it.
When I'm dancing, there's someone in front of me.
So when I'm doing the choreography.
I feel a little secure that I'm doing the right dance.
Yes.
But...
Sometimes
Let's make sure we remember
It's normal to have someone in front of you.
Look back? You mean look back?
Yes, that's right.
It's selfish, really.
It's really self-indulgent.
But there are moments when you're standing in the first row.
So that's how it happens?
Yes, I do.
That's when you're anxious, so you look at the people who are doing the furikomi.
And you say, "Oh, that's right.
And you say, "This is the right way.
That kind of thing.
Look at them, look at them, look at them.
It's the right way to check.
That kind of thing.
It's not that I like doing it with him because he remembers me.
If you forget, just look at the person and you'll see it.
That's amazing.
People in the front row wouldn't have thought of that.
That's right.
Soooo...
You haven't come up with that idea yet.
I didn't know it was still an idea.
I don't have that idea.
No, I don't.
Okay, well, here's the second question.
Okay, the second question is about the lessons of the variety show.
This is very important.
We've all been in a lot of variety shows.
Here is the quiz!
Mr. Otani says that he keeps one thing in mind when he watches VTRs.
What is it?
Here you go, Yoshimura.
Looking at the camera
Well, you see, Mr. Otani, that's not the level of it.
When you watch a VTR, you have to look at the camera.
You have to look at the VTR.
When the VTR is playing, it's not good to look at the camera.
Nagamatsu!
Keep commenting in a loud voice.
More, more, more!
Yes, Takanashi.
Grip with a wiggly grip to block the view of people around you
It's a mess!
It's fucked up.
No, it's not.
Come on, Hayashi
Fall off the chair when startled
Suddenly people disappear
Disappear
If it was a wipe...
Fujisaki
Whenever I leave a comment, I do it with a show of hands.
Who's going to stab me?
Yes, Natsune.
I'll do a play-by-play of the whole thing.
Aah! So close! But.
It's a little close, but I'd say more like...
Yes, Hayashi.
Well, when you say something, you say, "Pin mic this way.
Yes!
But, yes, yes.
Well, yes.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Specifically.
Yes, Takanashi.
You're holding someone else's pin mic.
Why is this? Why does Takanashi keep dropping people around him?
Mr. Otani, you're not that kind of person.
No, you can do this. You'll probably get an answer.
Yes, Saito.
He talks like a second voice.
Oh! No, but I think you've already answered correctly.OH!!! No, but you're already correct.
Then it is correct!
Yes.
The correct answer is to have a conversation with the narrator.
Yes, sir.
That's my grandma's, isn't it?
You mean grandma?
What does this mean?
Well, I do react during the VTR,
I thought it would be difficult to use it if it was used with the words in the VTR,
Narration...
That was a great nod. Everyone is doing this.
That's true.
I don't care what they say during the narration.
It's all mouth-to-mouth, mostly.
Ah.
I see.
But why don't you just make normal comments during the narration of the narration?
Is that not good enough?
To the microphone,
What happened in 1990? What happened in 1990?
What? What is it?
What is it? I was like, "Oh, what?
I didn't know that happened.
It's a tear-jerker.
It's a little tearful, but it's a big help.
Really?
It's easy to use.
No, I'm glad.
By the way, if you say it out loud, it will get on other people's mics,
If you're not sure, use a microphone.
It's like I'm being criticized.
I'm talking in a very loud voice even in the wipe-chee.
Today, Takeshi's microphone position is here.
I've never seen it before. I've never seen it before.
I'm sure Mike was wearing it here,
The commentator told me not to yell because it's a little too loud.
You've never seen it.
After all, all the talent's voices are on a different channel. They are on different channels.
You can turn it up or down on each channel,
So, during the VTR, you don't have to yell so loud.
Oh, so all you have to do is just watch in a small voice.
You just have to say what you think of it and you're in.
Oh, so that's how it is. I learned something too.
I think this is really important for everyone.
Let's review it together. To remember.
Let's do it.
Narrating and conversing.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Okay, let's go to the third question. Gaya-san, please.
Yes, the third question is a lesson on the necessities of work.
Necessities.
Here is the quiz.
Please tell us why a hat is a necessity for you, Mr. Otani.
Is a hat used for recording? Not on a recording?
I definitely wear a hat when I go to the field.
Yes, I do.
Now, let's go to number seven.
I stuff my stuff in the hat.
No, no, no.
This is Mr. Yanagi's system.
Candy.
I'll put candy in it.
I don't do candy.
Come on, Saito.
You're going to get hit with a "tsukkomi".
Oh, yeah.
I'll protect my head.
But that's a recording.
The point is that you're wearing it before the recording.
Come on, Mr. Fujii.
It's in good shape in case bird droppings fall on the way.
With a cover.
Cover it up.
Come on, Yoshijima.
I'm really wearing a wink.
They won't notice. They won't know.
It has a meaning.
Yes, Takanashi.
It makes you look like a top celebrity.
Oh.
So they can show that they have to disguise themselves?
Like branding.
It's a little more than that.
I don't know.
It's like an item to make people like you.
An item to make people like you.
A string.
When someone passes by or greets you, you should be polite by wearing a hat like this.
It is correct.
It's great.
It's just as it is.
It's to give the impression that you are greeting someone.
Wait a minute. The way you say it.
It's just for show.
Is it not?
Actually, I met Mr. Sakuma here in the hallway.
First of all, I don't have to wear a hat when I leave the dressing room because I have already set my hair after the show.
But the staff would see me off on the way home, so I would put it on once in the dressing room.But the staff will see me off on my way home, so I will wear it once in the dressing room.
You don't have to wear this hat, do you?
Yes, you don't have to wear it.
In fact, yes.
I'm wearing a hat that I don't really need to wear,
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It was the height of the staging, wasn't it?
The guy doing the staging was this high.
The batting average is high.
The hitting point is very high.
But if he did that, I would think he was a very nice person.
How about the staff?
Don't you like him as a TV personality?
But maybe just a little bit.
I would like to work with this person again.
I remember people whose greetings are very impressive.
Who do you remember?
That's exactly what Momoguro means.
Oh, I remember Momoguro from the first time I worked with him.
Momokuro was great from the first time I worked with him.
Amazing, indeed.
That must have been a learning experience.
Ha-ha-ha.
He said that greetings are a matter of course.
Greetings are a matter of course.
I guess you could say that a voice that cannot be heard is not a voice at all, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's what I mean.
The voice, plus the gesture, should be easy to understand.
Now then, everyone, let's do adverbs. Se-no.
I'm going to use the hat to create a face that says hello.
Wait a minute.
If I put this up short, it's going to be a big problem.
Ha-ha-ha.
Ms. Kakutani, when you were working as an idol, did you ever think about changing something here from other people, or did you think that you could do your best if you cared about this part, rather than just standing out?
I was overtaken and overtaken by junior members for a long time, but I always thought that the result would come 10 years later.
I always wondered who would be left in 10 years.
Isn't the entertainment business tough?
If you do it with this kind of feeling, you can consider each good thing and each bad thing now as a memory or an experience, right?
Yes, I can.
Even Mr. Otani didn't understand the attention he was getting from the pond, did he?
No, it's true. I was invited on the side.
That's right.
I wasn't invited as the main performer.
Originally, the top members of the general election were scheduled to participate in the Music Festival, but since one of them was in a variety show, I wasn't scheduled to participate in the Music Festival.
Is that so?
You came even though the music festival and your birthday had nothing to do with each other?
Yes, I did.
It has nothing to do with the festival.
But I was the most droning, interesting, and funny of all the variety staff, and they were like, "Who is that?
A regular.
It was amazing.
In the end, we even made it to the music festival.
Wow!
We had a group called "Ike-no-Mizu Selection.
Pond's Water Selection.
Mr. Omaehara made it for us.
Pond Water Selection.
Were there any members who were great among those you worked with?
Well, I was Sashi Harari's. But at first, I didn't get much attention.
But at first, I didn't get that much attention.
That's right.
But the reason why they paid attention to me was because of my interesting writing on my Ameba blog.
Oh, so it was a blog.
That's right. Akimoto-sensei told me that I should update my blog 100 times in one day tomorrow because I was so interesting.
Wow!
That's right, an Ameba blog. And he did it. He posted 100 interesting blogs,
I thought, "How can this person not sell?
It's an Ameba blog.
You never know where opportunities lie.
You really don't know what triggers the attention.
No, it's amazing.
So, how was it? How was your day-to-day? You should hear what he has to say.
Wow, that really hit home.
Yeah, I know.
I thought I was saying hello without a hat on.
Oh, I should have worn a hat.
Thank you for seeing me through to the end today.
Thank you.
It was!